Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/kaushalvish (LinkedIn) hellokaushal750.github.io/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Go (Programming Language)
MySQL
Next.js

Languages

Hindi (Native or Bilingual) English (Full Professional)

Certifications

Arduino
Zoom Marathon Challenge
AutoCad

Kaushal Vishwakarma

Software Developer

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Summary

Hello,

After 12th I decided to do engineering in IT, but just because of 2 marks less in entrance exam(CET)

I was not eligible to get the admission in IT and I ended up getting admission in Mechanical.

Mechanical became much interesting field for me to built the analytical skill. During college I came across machine design software's like AutoCAD and Solid works. I was only in my 2nd year when the pandemic broke and the entire nation and world went into a lockdown. That gave me plenty of time to explore new things and enhance my creativity. It led me to explore design. So I joined Milestone Institute to learn AutoCAD and Solid works.

But because of pandemic I didn't have much knowledge about practical work and also there was not higher chances of job in Mechanical. I decided to switch my career as web developer, I have always interested in IT field.

After my graduation I was eagerly searching for a good web development course and I came across an advertisement and when I did some research about the institute, I found the course really interesting. Soon after I enrolled myself in full stack web development course (by Masai School).

Currently I am working as Software Developer in Tezminds.

Experience

TezMinds Software Pvt. Ltd.
Software Developer
September 2023 - Present (1 year 10 months)
Pune. Maharashtra. India

IKS Health
Junior Revenue Cycle Representative
June 2022 - September 2022 (4 months)

Navi Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

My first job after graduation was in IKS Health as a Junior revenue cycle representative. It was a great experience to be a part of it. Learned basic of about how health insurance works in the US. IKS Health is a company that helps US doctors to get their payment from health insurance. I realized that my strengths and weaknesses were not aligned with the requirements of the post. I decided it was best that I left at the earliest and started to hunt for more relevant opportunities.

Education

Masai

Full Stack Web Development, Information Technology · (September 2022 - July 2023)

Thakur College of Engineering & Technology BE, Mechanical Engineering (2018 - 2022)